

# Sivakumar Tadisetti

Software Engineer / Frontend Web Developer



# **Professional Summary**

With over 5+ years of experience, seeking the position of Frontend Engineer to further enhance organizational worth owing to knowledge in HTML5, CSS, SCSS, JavaScript, Typescript, Angular 2+, Angular material design, Git, Ajax, JSON and Bootstrap



## **Work History**

2018-11 -Current

# Software Engineer

Infor, Hyderabad, Telengana

- Worked on features, bugs and improvements of the company owned product Birst
- Participated in team meetings and gathering the requirements and implemented the code from designs

2018-03 -2018-10

# Software Engineer

Abhra Cloud Software Solutions, Hyderabad, Telengana

 Worked with software development and testing team members to design and develop robust solutions to meet client requirements for functionality, scalability and performance.

2017-09 -2018-03

# Full Stack PHP Developer

Zetoe, Hyderabad, Telengana

 Contributed ideas and suggestions in team meetings and delivered updates on deadlines, designs and enhancements.

2015-08 -2017-08

# Associate Software Engineer

Osmosys Software Solutions, Hyderabad, Telengana

- Worked on different client projects like Riveng, Baseline using technologies like Javascript, HTML, CSS and PHP
- Collaborated with cross-functional development team members to analyze potential system solutions based on evolving client requirements.



## Education

2011-03 -2015-04

## **B.Tech: Computer Science**

Vishnu Institute of Technology - Bhimavaram

Percentage: 70

2009-03 -2011-02 Intermediate: M.P.C

Aditya Junior College - Bhimavaram

Percentage: 88.6

2008-03 -2009-03 S.S.C: 10th

A.R.K.R Municipal High School - Bhimavaram

Percentage: 89.33



### Address

Hyderabad, Telangana, 500055

## **Phone**

830-963-4801

#### F-mail

sivakumar.tadisetti@gmail.com



Javascript

Angular

Angular

Excellent

Excellent

Very Good CSS

Very Good SCSS

Good ReactJS

Good NodeJS

Good